
/*https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Solar_System*/
var questions = [
    {
        question: "How many moons in our solar system are larger than Murcery?",
        answer: ['<li class="answer correct">2</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">1</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">5</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">10</li>']
    },
    {
        question: "When did the our solar system form?",
        answer: ['<li class="answer incorrect">14 billion yeards ago.</li>',
                '<li class="answer correct">4.6 billion years ago.</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">3 billion years ago.</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">40 billion years ago.</li>']

    },
    {
        question: "Which planet is an ice giant?",
        answer:['<li class="answer incorrect">Saturn</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Venus</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Earth</li>',
                '<li class="answer correct">Neptune</li>']

    },
    {
        question: "Which planet is an ice giant?",
        answer:['<li class="answer incorrect">Jupiter</li>',
                '<li class="answer correct">Uranus</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Mercury</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Mars</li>']

    },
    {
        question: "Which planet is a gas giant?",
        answer:['<li class="answer incorrect">Mars</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Earth</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Venus</li>',
                '<li class="answer correct">Jupiter</li>']

    },
    {
        question: "Which planet is a gas giant?",
        answer: ['<li class="answer incorrect">Neptune</li>',
                '<li class="answer correct">Saturn</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Uranus</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Venus</li>']

    },
    {
        question: "What is between Mars and Jupiter?",
        answer: ['<li class="answer correct">Astroid belt</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">A teapot</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Earth</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">A horde of alien invaders</li>']

    },
    {
        question: "Whose red Tesla is orbiting the sun?",
        answer: ['<li class="answer incorrect">Larry Page</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Jeff Bezos</li>',
                '<li class="answer correct">Elon Musk</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Sergey Brin</li>']

    },
    {
        question: "Who is funding Blue Origin?",
        answer: ['<li class="answer incorrect">A rich squirrel</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Elon Musk</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">What is Blue Origin?</li>',
                '<li class="answer correct">I am thanks to Amazon Prime!</li>',]

    },
    {
        question: "Which opject is in the Astriod belt?",
        answer:['<li class="answer correct">Ceres</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Pluto</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">The Moon</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Mars</li>']

    },
    {
        question: "Which object is in the Kuiper belt?",
        answer: ['<li class="answer incorrect">Ceres</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">Mars</li>',
                '<li class="answer correct">Pluto</li>',
                '<li class="answer incorrect">The Moon</li>']

    },
]


 

